<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>TRAP.LOL</title>
    <link>https://blog.trap.lol/</link>
    <description>Recent content on TRAP.LOL</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-gb</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 13 Nov 2023 20:43:24 +0200</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://blog.trap.lol/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Neutral</title>
      <link>https://blog.trap.lol/posts/neutral/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Nov 2023 20:43:24 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.trap.lol/posts/neutral/</guid>
      
      <description>Yes / No / Maybe </description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Trip Report 01</title>
      <link>https://blog.trap.lol/posts/trip-report-01/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Nov 2023 20:47:44 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.trap.lol/posts/trip-report-01/</guid>
      
      <description>2023-10-08 - 2g Albino Penis Envy I didn&amp;rsquo;t start the day thinking I was going to be doing mushrooms. It started like most Sundays for me. I woke up, studied a bit and then went to watch TV in the living room. I watched Dr K. and in the video he talks about people requiring idle time in the mind to help process emotions. I took this advice seriously, but thought I would &amp;ldquo;intensify&amp;rdquo; the idle time with the use of mushrooms.</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Your Fault</title>
      <link>https://blog.trap.lol/posts/your-fault/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Nov 2023 20:44:56 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.trap.lol/posts/your-fault/</guid>
      
      <description>Mental illness is so strange. You cant see it, you doubt it is there, no one really seems to believe you, even you don&amp;rsquo;t know if you are being true. I cant decide if I am responsible for the way I feel. Obviously my overall attitude towards life will impact how I feel, but is it really as simple as just deciding &amp;ldquo;now I will be positive&amp;rdquo;. That seems to be what everyone else implies when I talk to them about how I feel.</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Identity</title>
      <link>https://blog.trap.lol/posts/identity/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Nov 2023 20:39:14 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.trap.lol/posts/identity/</guid>
      
      <description>Self-identity refers to the way in which individuals define themselves and perceive themselves in relation to the world around them. At its core, self-identity is about understanding who we are, what makes us unique, and how we fit into the broader social and cultural contexts in which we exist. So, who are you? What does it mean when that identity shatters, the moments that follow after you realize who you thought yourself to be is completely incorrect.</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Brain Fog</title>
      <link>https://blog.trap.lol/posts/brain-fog/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Nov 2023 20:32:57 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.trap.lol/posts/brain-fog/</guid>
      
      <description>My head makes me feel like a sailor in the middle of the ocean on a foggy night with no lighthouse in sight. Like water having to move from one side of a sponge through to the other side. Every thought being caught in a barrier that rips them apart. Like muddy water I can not see my thoughts. They speed away faster than I can move. They change direction in attempts to evade me.</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Main Character</title>
      <link>https://blog.trap.lol/posts/main-character/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Nov 2023 20:26:43 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.trap.lol/posts/main-character/</guid>
      
      <description>I grew up with a steady stream of media, promoting a protagonist, someone who is the centre of all attention, someone around which the world revolves. No wonder I had all these big ideas and plans, believing I, somehow me, is the centre of the universe. Placing such importance on the actions I choose, as it would affect anyone and everyone … such bullshit The truth is, even on a small scale, my life means nothing to many.</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hello World</title>
      <link>https://blog.trap.lol/posts/hello-world/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Nov 2023 13:30:09 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.trap.lol/posts/hello-world/</guid>
      
      <description>Introduction I am Tristan Phillips, a nobody who is looking to just play around on the internet.
What will I post here? My thoughts and experiences, and anything in-between
What do I expect? This is simply a kind of public journal for me, to keep track of my life in a way that I control the information being shared. Even if it is very public and personal to me. I hope to be able to look back on this in the future and see how far I have come</description>
      
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
