<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on TRAP.LOL</title>
    <link>https://blog.trap.lol/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on TRAP.LOL</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-gb</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 28 Nov 2023 14:15:14 +0200</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://blog.trap.lol/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Focus</title>
      <link>https://blog.trap.lol/posts/focus/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Nov 2023 14:15:14 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.trap.lol/posts/focus/</guid>
      
      <description>The chief task in life is simply this: To identify and separate matters so that I can say clearly to myself which are externals not under my control, and which have to do with the choices I actually control. Where then do I look for good and evil? Not uncontrollable externals, but within myself to the choices that are my own
-Epictetus, Discourses, 2.5.4-5 Our focus should be on that which we can control, not that which we cannot.</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Guilt</title>
      <link>https://blog.trap.lol/posts/guilt-#-edit-conflict-2023-11-27-n23jsjc-%23/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Nov 2023 07:07:50 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.trap.lol/posts/guilt-#-edit-conflict-2023-11-27-n23jsjc-%23/</guid>
      
      <description>Why do I feel guilt? Seriously, whenever I do something for myself, I feel a sense of guilt. Is it because I am not doing the right thing? I am not doing what I am supposed to? The shame I feel, for doing something for myself, because I can, makes my stomach turn. Doing something that is not for my, or someone elses future benefit. It drives me insane. I cant enjoy it, I cant appreciate it, all I do is feel guilt and shame.</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Guilt</title>
      <link>https://blog.trap.lol/posts/guilt/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Nov 2023 07:07:50 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.trap.lol/posts/guilt/</guid>
      
      <description>Why do I feel guilt? Seriously, whenever I do something for myself, I feel a sense of guilt. Is it because I am not doing the right thing? I am not doing what I am supposed to? The shame I feel, for doing something for myself, because I can, makes my stomach turn. Doing something that is not for my, or someone elses future benefit. It drives me insane. I cant enjoy it, I cant appreciate it, all I do is feel guilt and shame.</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Future</title>
      <link>https://blog.trap.lol/posts/future/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Nov 2023 20:55:23 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.trap.lol/posts/future/</guid>
      
      <description>I live in the future, and I dont mean, &amp;ldquo;Oh I constantly look towards the future&amp;rdquo;.
I mean I actually live in the future. I see it happening, feel it happening, watch it happen. Living my life today, watching the me of tomorrow. Theres nothing like this. It brings a wave of sadness. Watching yourself from the present looking towards the future looking back towards the past. It brings joy as well though, a sense of relief, that every moment now, will be okay.</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Aggro</title>
      <link>https://blog.trap.lol/posts/aggro/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Nov 2023 11:02:24 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.trap.lol/posts/aggro/</guid>
      
      <description>Sometimes a person gets mad.
Mad for no reason at all.
An innocents voice, brings out the worst in you.
A person unknowingly destroying real estate within your mind.
You don&amp;rsquo;t know why, and that makes the situation even worse for yourself.
An impulsive panic, upbringing deep trauma, perhaps unrelated to the victim.
Why can one person make you feel this way, why can you treat an individual with so much injustice.</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>When do you die?</title>
      <link>https://blog.trap.lol/posts/die/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Nov 2023 20:42:33 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.trap.lol/posts/die/</guid>
      
      <description>Is it possible to die before your death?
And I don&amp;rsquo;t mean the classical, no-feelings die, like we all have.
I mean to die and then to live life.
To live as though you have already died.
To live life knowing you will one day not be able to look back to today, but moments before then you will.
To live life as though you are talking to that you in the future, and telling them, everything is going to be okay.</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Neutral</title>
      <link>https://blog.trap.lol/posts/neutral/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Nov 2023 20:43:24 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.trap.lol/posts/neutral/</guid>
      
      <description>Yes / No / Maybe Why can one be in two contradictory states at the same time. Being completely aware that your states conflict, yet not feeling able to change it. More than wanting either state, more like being content with either state. Accepting one or the other, not rejecting either, but being in a place of peace regardless. It makes you positive, brightens your day, gives you hope. You wonder about both possibilities, daydreaming.</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Trip Report 01</title>
      <link>https://blog.trap.lol/posts/trip-report-01/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Nov 2023 20:47:44 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.trap.lol/posts/trip-report-01/</guid>
      
      <description>2023-10-08 - 2g Albino Penis Envy I didn&amp;rsquo;t start the day thinking I was going to be doing mushrooms. It started like most Sundays for me. I woke up, studied a bit and then went to watch TV in the living room. I watched Dr K. and in the video he talks about people requiring idle time in the mind to help process emotions. I took this advice seriously, but thought I would &amp;ldquo;intensify&amp;rdquo; the idle time with the use of mushrooms.</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Your Fault</title>
      <link>https://blog.trap.lol/posts/your-fault/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Nov 2023 20:44:56 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.trap.lol/posts/your-fault/</guid>
      
      <description>Mental illness is so strange. You cant see it, you doubt it is there, no one really seems to believe you, even you don&amp;rsquo;t know if you are being true. I cant decide if I am responsible for the way I feel. Obviously my overall attitude towards life will impact how I feel, but is it really as simple as just deciding &amp;ldquo;now I will be positive&amp;rdquo;. That seems to be what everyone else implies when I talk to them about how I feel.</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Identity</title>
      <link>https://blog.trap.lol/posts/identity/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Nov 2023 20:39:14 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.trap.lol/posts/identity/</guid>
      
      <description>Self-identity refers to the way in which individuals define themselves and perceive themselves in relation to the world around them. At its core, self-identity is about understanding who we are, what makes us unique, and how we fit into the broader social and cultural contexts in which we exist. So, who are you? What does it mean when that identity shatters, the moments that follow after you realize who you thought yourself to be is completely incorrect.</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Brain Fog</title>
      <link>https://blog.trap.lol/posts/brain-fog/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Nov 2023 20:32:57 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.trap.lol/posts/brain-fog/</guid>
      
      <description>My head makes me feel like a sailor in the middle of the ocean on a foggy night with no lighthouse in sight. Like water having to move from one side of a sponge through to the other side. Every thought being caught in a barrier that rips them apart. Like muddy water I can not see my thoughts. They speed away faster than I can move. They change direction in attempts to evade me.</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Main Character</title>
      <link>https://blog.trap.lol/posts/main-character/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Nov 2023 20:26:43 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.trap.lol/posts/main-character/</guid>
      
      <description>I grew up with a steady stream of media, promoting a protagonist, someone who is the centre of all attention, someone around which the world revolves. No wonder I had all these big ideas and plans, believing I, somehow me, is the centre of the universe. Placing such importance on the actions I choose, as it would affect anyone and everyone … such bullshit The truth is, even on a small scale, my life means nothing to many.</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hello World</title>
      <link>https://blog.trap.lol/posts/hello-world/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Nov 2023 13:30:09 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.trap.lol/posts/hello-world/</guid>
      
      <description>Introduction I am Tristan Phillips, a nobody who is looking to just play around on the internet.
What will I post here? My thoughts and experiences, and anything in-between
What do I expect? This is simply a kind of public journal for me, to keep track of my life in a way that I control the information being shared. Even if it is very public and personal to me. I hope to be able to look back on this in the future and see how far I have come</description>
      
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
